Art Collins Collection ARC.0001
Library and Archives
- Series I: Iggy Pop Legal Papers, 1995-2004 and undated
  - MVO Limited 2000 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Alan Roth / Florida Guy (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Tim McGregor correspondence (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Lee Solters correspondence (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Escape from Hollywood (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Goodyear AD script (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Death in Vegas (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Hollywood Affair / Hollywood Goes Wild (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - "Girls of New York" Cacharel Fragrances (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - "Penetration" Intimacy movie (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - "Lust for Life" Sugar and Spice movie (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - The Doors Project / Elektra contract (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - "Lust for Life" Rock Radio Volume 1 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Virgin Germany (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Solo Summer tour, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Call sheets (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Gelman contract (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - European tour (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - "Lust for Life" Rock and Cinema (France) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - "The Passenger" Halvliter Rock (Norway) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - "Some Weird Sin" New Blood (Bug) (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - "The Passenger" 30 Days documentary (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - "Dirt” House of Wax (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - "Dog Food" Tomorrow Show (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - "The Passenger" Volvo Premium (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - "Little Know it All" The Right Stuff (Harley Davidson) (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - "Butt Town" The Fresh Prince of Bel Aire (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - "Little Know it All" Comp'd (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - "The Passenger" The Insider (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - "Success" Lords of Dogtown (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - "The Passenger" Chevrolet (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - "The Passenger" The Moguls (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - "Success" I Love the 90's (VH1) (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Dog" Coachella DVD (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - "Lust for Life" Guitar Hero Video Game (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - "Lust for Life" 1977 Great Funk Hits (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - "Beside You" Skate More Video (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - "Some Weird Sin" New Blood DVD (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - "Boogie Boy" Crossing Jordan (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - "The Passenger" The Weatherman (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Family Stone / Iggy poster (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - "Boogie Boy" (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - BBC Worldwide statements (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - "Lust for Life" The Moguls (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Lords of Dogtown (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Royal Caribbean (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - "The Passenger" Freaky Styley (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - "Little Electric Chair" Viva la Bam (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - "Dirt" House of Wax (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Underground Garage line-up (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - "New Weird Sin" New Blood (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Allaire studios (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - "Lust for Life" Cold Case (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Music Video distribution (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Brothers of the Head (4 Song) (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - "Candy" German film (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - "Lust for Life" Portugal wine ad (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - "The Passenger" Juniper Bank (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Punk! DVD (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - "Lust for Life" Dr. Vegas (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - "Whatever" Rock Energy (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - "The Passenger" This is TV Commercial (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - "Candy" German TV (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - "Lust for Life" Royal Caribbean (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Allaire studios (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - "The Passenger" 30 Days Documentary (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Dog" XXX film (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - "Lust for Life" World's Greatest Artist (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - "Wild Child" Friday's Rock and Roll (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Copyright renewals (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - "Candy" Nineties Complete (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - "The Passenger" Austrian TV (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - "Candy" Showtime 10 (Hungary) (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - "Search and Destroy" Brothers of the Head (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Lagig papers (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - MVO (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Grumble (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - MVO Summer (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - "Lust for Life" Drive compilation (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - "Funtime" TV's Greatest Moments (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - August 2001 Euro wrap-up (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Tibo Pinsardo / Stooges documentary (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Most Important TV Moments (UK) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - VH1 Music and Sexuality (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - "Nightclubbing" Shyne (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - "China Girl" VH1 Storytellers (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - "Lust for Life" MTV Private Wrestler (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - "The Passenger" Waking Life Film (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - "Search and Destroy" 10 Shocking Moments (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - "Raw Power/Shake Appeal" 25 Years of Punk (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - "Nightclubbing" 25 Years of Punk (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - "Lust for Life" Nikki (TV Show) (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - "Lust for Life" World's Greatest Beer Songs (Australia) (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - "The Passenger" Guitar Club Classics (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - "The Passenger" Complete History of Punk (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - "The Passenger" French Fried Music (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - "Lust for Life" Loaded: Very Best Indies (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - "Lust for Life" Best Supporting Anthems (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - "I Need Somebody" Queer as Folk (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - "Lust for Life" Third Watch (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - "Lust for Life" Best Beer Songs (New Zealand) (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - "Lust for Life" Ultimate Rock (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - "Lust for Life" Arrow Classic Rock (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - "The Passenger" Cespa Spain (Advertising) (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Hollywood Affair / Hollywood Goes Wild (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - "The Passenger" Absolute Rock Classics (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - "Louie Louie" Cover Hits CD (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - "Search and Destroy" Chili Peppers DVD (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - "Lust for Life" NBC Third Watch (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - "The Passenger" Burning Annie (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - "The Passenger" Swedish Movie (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Gary Bass/ Chop Chop film synopsis (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Anthill Trading statement (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Controversy Films / The Real Kids (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Bug Music / Gaumont 2001 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Nascar / Sig Sigworth (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Petra Wolf letter (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - The Detroit Experiment (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Steve Smith / FOX (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - European Tour final report (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Solo reports to Grumble Corporation (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - US tour, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - The Detroit Experiment (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - "I Need Somebody" Queer as Folk (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - "The Passenger" Party Explosion (Sweden) (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - "Avenue B" Music is the Night (Korea) (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - "Lust for Life" Kellogg's Vive (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Swedish TV / Great Pleasures in Life (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - "The Passenger" Waking Life (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - "Lust for Life" Mitsubishi CD (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - "Candy" EMI Australia (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - "Lust for Life/The Passenger" HMV Box Set (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - "Real Wild Child" Out of the Box (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - L'Espresso / "Lust for Life" (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - "Death is Certain" Crossing Jordan (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - "Lust for Life" Gilmore Girls (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - "China Girl" Rock and Roll Jeopardy (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - "The Passenger" Ultimate 70's (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - "Lust for Life" Flash Hits Greece (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - "The Passenger" 156 Tracks (Surf/Skate) (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - "Sixteen" German compilation (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - "Avenue B" Hot Tracks in Autumn (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - TV's Greatest Moments / Dinah Shore (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - "Wild America" Big Day Out (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - "I'll Be Seeing You" Listen to This Picture (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Ultimate Iggy / Hip-O Records (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - "I'm Bored" Molson Dry (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Royal Caribbean amendment option (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - "Lust for Life" Nikki (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - Tour expenses (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - Bug Music summary statement (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - "Old Grey Whistle" Test DVD letter (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Jimi Hendrix house for sale (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Grammy's Art of Music (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Virgin Atlantic (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Jim Fitzgerald / book agent (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Ted Talvitie / puppet maker (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Stuff Release / Nina release (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Detroit Pistons ad agency (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - David Letterman thank you note (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Nina Simon / Moosehead's Mom (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Mid Summer promo (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Fall tour promo requests (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Arista royalties (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Kris Kramski letter (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Soundscan Reports "Beat 'em Up" (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Randi Kamhi deposition (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Virgin promo domestic (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Virgin promo international (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Pam Jones name change (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - "I Need More" French book (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - "The Passenger" New World Disorder (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Freddy got Fingered (Tom Green Movie) (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - "I'll Be Seeing You" Jazz on Cinema Two (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - "Lust for Life" Nikki Cox (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - "The Passenger" As Heard on TV (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - "Lust for Life” Kellogg's Canada (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Save the Last Dance (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - "Lust for Life” Armed Forces campaign (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Jonas Ackerland Movie "Spun" (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Apple Computer / Marie Conte (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Glenn Max / U.K Meltdown (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Royal Caribbean Bug renewal (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - "Lust for Life" Drew Carey Show (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - "The Passenger" Best Rock Anthems (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - "Real Wild Child" Axion Beach Rock (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - "Ann" Sample / Super Furry Animals (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - "China Girl" Rock and Roll Jeopardy (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - "Aisha” Playstation (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - "Lust for Life” Kellogg's Vive Cereal (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - "Lust for Life" MTV's Private Wrestler (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Guinness Draught / Bug music (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - "The Passenger" Proximus (Belgium) (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - "Search and Destroy" VH1's The List (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Miller Draft success (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - "Lust for Life" Essential Soundtracks (South Africa) (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - "Living on the Edge of the Night" Was it New (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - "The Passenger" Driving Rock Camp (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - "Lust for Life" Ontario Power (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - "Lust for Life" V2 Records (Japan) (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - VH1: 25 Years of Punk (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - "Lust for Life" As Seen on TV (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Success (B) Miller Genuine Draft (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Freddie Got Fingered (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Warehouse Studios Vancouver, Canada (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - "I'm Sick of You" Lyrics (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Conde Nast Display (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Bomp/Bug merchandise royalties (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Final U.S. tour report (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Canal and Belgium Concert TV rights (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Sig Sigworth correspondence (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Walmart artist card (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Virgin deadlines (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Mask the Mob / Bug and Virgin (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - "The Passenger" Classico de Classics (Argentina) (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - "Candy" Classico de Classics (Argentina) (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Joey Ramone Project / David Frey (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Laurel Canyon film photograph (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Mandy Stein / Journeyman's Pictures Movie release (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Rock It Cargo (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Apple Computers Fall 2001 ad option (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Microsoft memo (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Microsoft XBOX game (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - "Beat em Up" Gotham MultiMedia Game (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - "The Passenger" XBOX soundtrack (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Eric Benson / American Express (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Eric Benson / telephone charges (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - "Gimme Danger" Boss Clothing (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - "Gimme Danger" Option: To Each His Own (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - "Search and Destroy" Red Hot Chili Peppers DVD (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - "Search and Destroy" Sky TV (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - BMX II Multimedia game (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Laurel Canyon movie posters (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Kris Kramski / Larry Flint film (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Fabienne Reichenbach (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - "Moet Chandon" Sophie Megrous (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Solo Summer dates (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - "Playbook" Newspaper (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - MVO Summer dates (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Bug Statement, July to September 2002 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - MTV Latin America Awards show (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Christmas cards (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Dog" Prey for Rock and Roll (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Dog" Doggie Style Sample (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - "Avenue B" This is Rock (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - "No Fun" Dallas and Rusty (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Fastlane / FOX TV Show (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - "Wild America" Hottest of Hot (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Peter Tosh / VH1 Behind the Music (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Ian Maclagen correspondence (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Brick by Brick / Caesar Two Pack (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - "Cold Metal" David Letterman Show (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Floyd Peluce Monthly Reports (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Tina Turner DVD (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Mondo Picasso Script (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - "Mask" Daredevil (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - "Raw Power" 16 Years (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Reflections of Evil DVD Promo (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - "I'm Sick of You" Quitting Shelby (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - GHS strings (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Skydog Records (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - "Tonight" Janis and John (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - "My Baby Wants to Rock and Roll" Rock! Australia (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - "Sick of You" Short film (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - "I Need Somebody" Witchblade (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - "Beside You" Alternative Moments 2 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - "I'll Be Seeing You" Doc Dog Brazil (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - "Nightclubbing" Fiat Holland (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - "Nightclubbing" DOA Film (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Best of Bowie DVD release (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Grind costume department (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - "Candy" EMI Brazil (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - "Candy" Virgin Records 20th Anniversary (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - "Candy" Killer Barbies (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - "China Girl" VH1 Sexiest (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - "China Girl" American Idol (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - "China Girl” Last Call With Carson Daly (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - "Gimme Danger'' Dogtown and Z-Boys (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - "Lust for Life" song licenses (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - "The Passenger" song licenses (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - "Search and Destroy" song licenses (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Solo, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
  - Stooges gigs domestic (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Stooges gigs international (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - TMI 2002 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Solo offers (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Call sheets (Box 21, Folder 7-13)
  - Fuji Rock Festival 2003 books (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Skull Ring second file (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Codikow and Carroll billing, December 2002 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - "I’m Sick of You" School of Rock (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - "Candy" My Party Mix (Australia) (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Bug (1975) Copyright renewals (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Rock and Roll Hall of Fame contract renewal (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Black Flag / Memphis Three (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Debbie Strichhartz "Monster's and Angels" (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Boss Martins (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Don Ahn / Book Blurb (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Jean Montiel / French CD (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - "Boots" Producer agreement (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - "The Passenger" EMI Heroes (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - "Lust for Life" Discotheque Ideale (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - "In the Death Car" Turkish Beer (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - "Lust for Life" Classic Rock Tracks (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - "Beside Me" Alternative Moments (EMI Australia) (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - "Kill City"/"Five Foot One" Tales from the Crypt (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - "The Passenger" Back to Mine (UK) (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - "Girls" Sorority Life / MTV Promo (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - "The Passenger" Pro BMX 11 Multimedia Game (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - "The Passenger" DJ Jet Poland (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - "Lust for Life" Mobilkom (Austria cell phones) (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - "Raw Power" Leap of Faith #103 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - "China Girl' Bowie by request (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - "Five Foot One" Tales from the Crypt (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - "Lust for Life" Air Guitar Anthems (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - "Lust for Life" Rock Der Rykker (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - "Lust for Life" A Night at the Movies (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - " The Passenger" New Wave Classics (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - "Living on the edge of the Night" (Spain) (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - "The Passenger" Pop Classics (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - "Lust for Life" A Premium Request (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - "Houston is Hot Tonight" ESPN (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - "China Girl" Rock and Roll Jeopardy (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - "Lust for Life" Punk Compilation Virgin Europe (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - "Funtime/Lust for Life" Tony Scott (It's a Guy Thing) (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - "Mask" Dare Devil Movie (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - "I Need Somebody"VH1 Ultimate LPs (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - "Search and Destroy" VH1 Ultimate LPs (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - "Sixteen" My Life with Morrissey (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - "Lust for Life" Renault (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - "I'll Be Seeing You" Music Plus (Korea) (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - "Lust for Life" Punk the Jubilee (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - "The Passenger" Punk the Jubilee (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - "The Passenger" Mitsubishi 2002 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - "Lust for Life" No Spitting Compilation (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - "The Passenger" High Voltage Rock (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - "Gimme Danger" Dogtown Soundtrack (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Nigel Scott / UK Bt Advertisement (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Rascal Media Academy Awards (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Meltdown (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Slash / David Helfant (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - HBO Sports (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - 2002 Soundscan (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - JOS Grain Pay Virgin UK (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Alain Lahana 2002 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - "Witchblade" Bug Music (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - "Lust for Life" Screen Cuts Compilation (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - "The Passenger" Screen Cuts Compilation (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - "Bang Bang" Laurel Canyon (Bug) (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - "Raw Power" Leap of Faith (Song/Bug) (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - "Lust for Life" The Beautiful Game (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - "The Passenger" Punk Box Set (UK) (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - "Nightclubbing" Hits from Flicks (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - "Lust for Life" Hits from Flicks (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - "Lust for Life" New Wave Classics (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Royal Caribbean 3rd renewal (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - "Lust for Life" NBC 75th Anniversary (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - " The Passenger" Absolute Rock (Norway) (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - " Real Wild Child" Best Beer Drinking ( Australia) (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - "Aiesha" ATV Offroad Fury (Sony Computer) (Box 22, Folder 73)
  - Richard Karz Letter (April 1991) (Box 22, Folder 74)
  - "I'm Waiting for the Man" Steve Cole (Box 22, Folder 75)
  - Moet Champagne (Maria Conte) (Box 22, Folder 76)
  - Jim Fitzgerald correspondence (Box 22, Folder 77)
  - Press clips (Box 22, Folder 78)
  - "24 Hour Party People" Clip use (Box 22, Folder 79)
  - Santiago, Chile benefit (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Radical Media AMC Documentary (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Black Celebration / Jailbird Films (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - The New EMI (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Codikow and Carroll billing (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Wolfman Productions / Speaking Engagements (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Les belles Lettres contract (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Rollins Publications (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - "I Need More" Book Information (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - "The Vacation" Movie script (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Gary Bass / Chop Chop film (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Moby dinner special (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Richard Doctroff information (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Prey For Rock and Roll / Linda Cohen (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Q Magazine column request (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Concert on Top of the World request (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Gui Brigaudiot French web site (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - "Lust for Life" Best Alternative CD (South Africa) (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - "Lust for Life" The Sims House Party (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Belgium DVD request (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Belfort concert offer (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Keith Wood / Virgin Records correspondence (Box 23, Folder 22-24)
  - "Cold Metal" Radio Waves of the 80's (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - "Beside You" Alternative Moments (Australia) (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - "Lust for Life" L'Espresso Italy (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - "Idiot" EMI campaign (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Coffee and Cigarettes movie (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - "School of Rock" Wonderland (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - "Raw Power" Aloha Surf (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - "Lust for Life” Rugrats Go Wild (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - "No Fun" Lexus Germany (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Sylvie Simmons correspondence (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - "The Passenger" Escape Rock (France) (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - "Lust for Life" Rugrats Go Wild (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - "Search and Destroy" Wonderland (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Dog" Wonderland (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - "Aiesha" Wrong Turn (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - "Aiesha" Sonic Cinema (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - "Candy" Killer Barbies vs. Dracula (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - "Lust for Life" Munichie Music (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - "Candy" Mexico Nu Classics (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - "Little Know it All" Nokia/Cingular Wireless (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - "Search and Destroy" The Wire Season Two (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Rock and Roll Party DVD for Japanese band (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Kiss my Blood music video distributions (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - "Search and Destroy" I Got a Right / Helicopters Live (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - "Sick of You" School of Rock (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Rugrats Go Wild Bug Synch (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - "Candy" EMI Spain (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - "Search and Destroy" Haggard Soundtrack (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - "Lust for Life" Italy kiosk (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - "Lust for Life" Simpsons Promo (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers image use (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - "Candy" Hang the DJ Australia (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Royal Caribbean (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - "Raw Power" Stander (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Millenia Nove Bug Music (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - "Little Know it All" Thunder 2004 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Rugrats Go Wild consent letters (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - "The Passenger" Virgin Megamusic (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - "The Passenger" World's Best Beer Songs (Australia) (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Dog" History of New Music (Canada) (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - "Nightclubbing" Trolleywood (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - "Lust for Life" EMI Party Box Set (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - "Little Know it All” Electronic Game (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - "1970" Tony Hawk's Underground (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - "Search and Destroy" Wonderland (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - "Lust for Life" Overdrive Me Crazy (Belgium) (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - "Candy" Indie Anthems (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - "The Passenger" Best Air Guitar CD's (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Bug Statements, January to March 2003 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - "Lust for Life" EMI Gold Box (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - TV Eye / Budget Series (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - "The Passenger" Rockline Vol. 2 France (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - "Little Know it All" 46th Grammy's EMI (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - "Raw Power" Stander / Sony (Box 25, Folder 4)